[{"answer": "I was -- I'm an executive, and I've run several companies, but I've taken time off to be with my children.", "docId": "130610pmt", "aSentId": 32, "question": "What were you doing right up to the moment you saw this man?", "qSentId": 31}, {"answer": "And that's why I was in the area.", "docId": "130610pmt", "aSentId": 35, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 34}, {"answer": "I turn the corner and what I saw was a man with black hair in a Kevlar vest with a black shirt and a rifle standing on the corner, on the left-hand corner, motioning a girl in her car to come forward.", "docId": "130610pmt", "aSentId": 39, "question": "There you were, you were just driving along on your way to an audition and then suddenly, you see what?", "qSentId": 38}, {"answer": "I'm sitting in my office, my phone rings, it says my wife is calling, I pick it up, expecting a normal conversation about what time I'm going to be home and what we're going to do with the kids that night.", "docId": "130610pmt", "aSentId": 58, "question": "And, Russell, I mean, what was the first that you heard about this?", "qSentId": 57}, {"answer": "He had an automatic rifle.", "docId": "130610pmt", "aSentId": 63, "question": "Debra, I mean, what kind of gun was he using?", "qSentId": 62}, {"answer": "I know a bit about guns and I have shotguns at a range, so I know what they look like, but I've never seen somebody out on the street with an automatic rifle the way it was -- it was aimed at first the girl that he hijacked and then myself.", "docId": "130610pmt", "aSentId": 69, "question": "When you come face to face with that, had you ever as a couple had much thought about guns before this?", "qSentId": 68}, {"answer": "They fire incredibly quickly.", "docId": "130610pmt", "aSentId": 75, "question": "They fire incredibly quickly, don't they?", "qSentId": 74}, {"answer": "I feel very lucky to be alive.", "docId": "130610pmt", "aSentId": 93, "question": "You must feel incredibly lucky to be alive, don't you?", "qSentId": 92}, {"answer": "I would love to meet up with her.", "docId": "130610pmt", "aSentId": 124, "question": "Would you be prepared to do that?", "qSentId": 123}, {"answer": "I've always been very neutral in terms of gun control.", "docId": "130610pmt", "aSentId": 140, "question": "But nobody in Washington seems to care enough to do something about it?", "qSentId": 139}, {"answer": "I think Mr. Snowden had no right to arrogate to himself the right to decide where to strike the balance between liberty and security.", "docId": "130610pmt", "aSentId": 192, "question": "What is your reaction to Edward Snowden's decision to leak this information?", "qSentId": 191}, {"answer": "Well, the problem is, that once you start explaining to al Qaeda and Hezbollah how you are operating, they can avoid what you're doing, and you can't explain to the American people without explaining to Hezbollah and al Qaeda.", "docId": "130610pmt", "aSentId": 199, "question": "What do you believe the consequences of his decision could be at their worst?", "qSentId": 198}, {"answer": "OOLSEY: Well, they don't know everything about your online activity, because it's illegal --", "docId": "130610pmt", "aSentId": 211, "question": "Why should they?", "qSentId": 210}, {"answer": "It's illegal for them to take some steps with respect to it such as to get into the substance of the -- of the intercept.", "docId": "130610pmt", "aSentId": 214, "question": "But they could, right?", "qSentId": 213}, {"answer": "Well, from what I hear and what he's done, I mean, he's done a great service because he's telling the truth and this is what we are starved for.", "docId": "130610pmt", "aSentId": 225, "question": "You are a supporter of Edward Snowden and his actions, why?", "qSentId": 224}, {"answer": "Well, it depends on whether or not you want to preserve your country's ability to operate in a world of terrorism in which a lot of terrorist are very technically sophisticated.", "docId": "130610pmt", "aSentId": 252, "question": "It's palpably a breach, isn't it?", "qSentId": 251}, {"answer": "Given the fact that this system was put together by the people's elected representatives that it's been upheld by the courts.", "docId": "130610pmt", "aSentId": 270, "question": "-- 99.9 percent of the information being effectively seized here?", "qSentId": 269}, {"answer": "No, no, I absolutely do want to consider it.", "docId": "130610pmt", "aSentId": 281, "question": "They both have to be considered and you apparently -- Piers, not to want to consider security?", "qSentId": 280}, {"answer": "AUL: An awful lot of it, but it wouldn't be stopped.", "docId": "130610pmt", "aSentId": 291, "question": "If you had been president, are you in all seriousness telling me that you would have stopped all of this tracking of data in the way that the NSA has been doing it?", "qSentId": 290}, {"answer": "Well, I just --", "docId": "130610pmt", "aSentId": 309, "question": "What's wrong with that?", "qSentId": 308}, {"answer": "Certainly not, as far as we can tell.", "docId": "130610pmt", "aSentId": 354, "question": "Jeffrey Toobin, is anything that's happened here illegal?", "qSentId": 353}, {"answer": "That is a really good point.", "docId": "130610pmt", "aSentId": 397, "question": "But after the Gateway legislation called the Patriot Act, as an American I think anybody living in this country isn't any expectation of privacy and personal, you know, security -- isn't that really a moot point, the whole discussion about having any kind of privacy?", "qSentId": 396}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "130610pmt", "aSentId": 407, "question": "Well, basically, Ron Paul the president, would he utilize the information that was collected to prevent another 9/11 or what would he use in place of it?", "qSentId": 406}, {"answer": "I think that's pretty much a red herring, I mean, it's nonsense.", "docId": "130610pmt", "aSentId": 477, "question": "What do you say to that?", "qSentId": 476}, {"answer": "Well, there's no -- there's been no accusation at all that he's handing any kind of information to China.", "docId": "130610pmt", "aSentId": 493, "question": "How does that serve the American public interest?", "qSentId": 492}, {"answer": "I mean, that's an interesting question, but I think it side- steps a real issue, which is that he showed that the United States was violating multiple laws in both the Patriot Act and the Foreign Intelligence Surveillance Act.", "docId": "130610pmt", "aSentId": 501, "question": "But what is to stop -- what is to stop the Chinese doing that should they so wish if they get a hold of him first?", "qSentId": 500}, {"answer": "Yes, they can.", "docId": "130610pmt", "aSentId": 524, "question": "I mean, is he just a -- collection of metadata, like they claim, or can the people at the sharp end, and there are 1.4 million Americans currently working intelligence in some way who have that kind of access -- can they read e-mails, listen to phone calls, et cetera?", "qSentId": 523}]